Stephanie Fajardo

WEB DEVELOPER AND DESIGNER

404-907-3848

× s

stephfajardo@gatech.edu

9

Atlanta, GA

in

linkedin.com/in/stephfajardo

OTHER SKILLS

Video editing

Git/version control

Testing/debugging

Responsive design

120wpm typing speed

github.com/stephtf

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

My greatest strengths include my ability to problem solve, think creatively, and maintain a high level of self-motivation. I offer a diverse skillset as someone who is trained in full-stack web development, UX design, qualitative research, and education. I excel at organizing and completing large projects, meeting tight deadlines, and working cooperatively with others in teams.

EDUCATION

GEORGIA TECH FULL STACK CODING BOOTCAMP

3/9/2022

GOOGLE UX CERTIFICATE

11/19/2021

PHD, HISTORY

University of Michigan 08/21/2020

MA, TEACHING

University of Washington 12/16/2011

BA, HISTORY BA, ANTHROPOLOGY BA, SPANISH

University of Washington 6/11/2010

TOOLS

Figma
Adobe XD
Word
Excel
Powerpoint

LANGUAGES

English (native)
Spanish (proficient)
Tagalog (proficient)
French (beginner)

WORK EXPERIENCE

POSTDOCTORAL FELLOW

Georgia Institute of Technology / Atlanta, GA / August 2021 - Present

- Assembled Twitter API to analyze audience reception of 90 Day Fiancé
- Organized and examined archival sources related to US military families in the Philippines
- Developed an undergraduate course on US gender history

POSTDOCTORAL FELLOW

University of Michigan / Ann Arbor, MI / August 2020 - August 2021

- Planned a transnational panel on anti-Asian violence, bringing together scholars and activists from the US and Australia
- Wrote and presented a research paper on gender and anti-Asian violence
- Published three articles for SAGE Filipinx Studies Encyclopedia and a book review for the Journal of Asian Studies

RESEARCH SUPERVISOR

Bentley Historical Library / Ann Arbor, MI / May 2019 - August 2020

- Managed a large archival research project on the topic of US colonialism in the Philippines
- Facilitated research and digital skills workshops for undergraduates
- Oversaw the creation of an open-access, digital exhibit of archival findings

RESEARCH FELLOW AND LECTURER

University of Michigan / Ann Arbor, MI / August 2018 - May 2019

- Conducted oral interviews with subjects in Tagalog for a project on gender and US military history in the Philippines
- Designed and taught History 195, an introductory historical writing course
- Delivered lectures and led students in large-group discussion

SKILLS

CODING	UX DESIGN	RESEARCH
HTML	User Research	Qualitative Method
CSS	Wireframing	Interviewing
javascript	Prototyping	Data Management
node.js	Usability Studies	Affinity Mapping
express	Universal Design	Critical Analysis